Karenai
Let's go.
I'll be right back.
There.
Now I'm ready.
Alright, kid.
Before we get into it, there's
something I want to ask you.
What?
You didn't, you know, kill Vice
Commander Fanatio, did you?
She's alive.
She's being healed as we speak.
That's good.
Since you spared her life, I'll
return the favor and spare yours.
How disrespectful.
Why do you think that?
If you're this high up in the Cathedral,
you must be the commander
of the Integrity Knights.
Yeah?
What if I am?
What about the others?
Fanatio isn't the only knight.
Eldrie, the four Whirling Blades, Alice.
What about them?
Don't they matter?
I see.
You're taking that road.
How do I put this?
Eldrie is Alice's apprentice.
The four Whirling Blades, Dakira, Jace,
Holvren, and Jiro, they're Fanatios.
And her?
Well, she happens to be my apprentice.
It's not that I don't
care about the others.
It's just, I'm invested in Fanatio.
That's why if you killed her,
I'd be obliged to avenge her.
That's all there is to it.
Though, now that I think about it,
I guess little Alice does
look up to me as her mentor.
She's not the same as
she was six years ago,
when she first became
an apprentice knight.
If me and her went at it now, I
don't know who'd come out on top.
Anyway, seeing as how
Alice is as strong as me,
you must have snuck past her somehow.
But you won't be so lucky with me.
Come to think of it,
shouldn't there be two of you?
The Prime Senator said you had a partner.
I guess if he's not here with you,
that means he's off somewhere
keeping little Alice busy.
Yeah, he probably is.
I'm ready.
Let's get this over with.
I'm curious to see who will avenge you.
No one, kid.
I don't have a mentor.
Norkia style.
Lightning Slash.
Or it's something like it.
With his sword like that,
it'll take him an extra move or
two to activate the technique.
But if I use the Aincrad-style
Sonic Leap, I can strike him first.
Ah, now that's an interesting stance.
I've never seen it before.
Do you use combo attacks?
Maybe I do.
Maybe I don't.
Why do you care?
I don't.
It's just that there was a knight from the
Dark Territory who liked to use him, too.
I fought him a couple of times before.
I didn't like the
experience, to be honest.
My style's simple.
Doing all them flashy moves
is way too complicated.
Is that so?
Do you want me to fight like you then?
Using only conventional moves? Hell no.
You want to use combo attacks?
Go ahead.
I can handle anything you dish out, kid.
I should warn you, though.
I'm going to use my best move
first, and you ain't ready for it.
If his sword's already in perfect
control, then I've only got one chance.
As he activates his move,
I'll attack with Sonic Leap.
Taste the blade of Bercouli Synthesis 1.
On guard! Bercouli?
That ripple, it's where he just slashed.
Oof, talk about cutting it close.
The last thing I expected was for you
to come rushing in at me like that.
Sorry, kid.
I damn near killed you.
Yeah, I know you did.
But with what?
That was my best move,
just like I told you.
When I took that swing, I
wasn't just slicing air.
I was slicing a moment in
the future, so to speak.
Slicing the future?
The first time I saw a Dark
Knight use a combo attack
was just after I became an
Integrity Knight myself.
The sword techniques I
learned were all about putting
as much strength as I could
behind a single strike.
But sword techniques using
combination moves focus
on how to handle your enemy's
attacks and land hits.
It's pretty obvious which is
more practical than a fight.
Anyway, I got beat up
real good, but I survived.
Then I got to thinking how I could
land a hit against a combo user.
I found the answer with this thing.
Originally, it was part of a
divine object called a clock.
It used to hang on the wall
of the central cathedral.
It was here when the world was
first created, or so I was told.
It had a weird name.
The Pontifex called it System
Clock, or something like that.
When little Alice uses
her Osmanthus blade,
it cuts through the
horizontal axis of space.
But mine cuts the vertical axis of time.
Now it's got a new name,
the Time-Splitting Sword.
When he swung it, the force
of his strike stayed in place.
That means I don't have a
chance against him up close.
I'll have to use long-range attacks.
System call.
Connect armament.
Search archive...
Let me guess, you're setting yourself
up to attack from a distance, right?
Everyone who sees that move does.
Same goals for all the Integrity
Knights that came after me,
including Fanatio and Alice.
Once they saw that move,
they picked long-range,
perfect control to try and deal with it.
I can't blame them.
Trying to bring me down got to be
sort of a contest between them.
But I never lost.
I sparred with all of them, and
here I am, still their commander.
Well, if one of them does take
my job, it'll probably be Alice.
I sure am looking forward to this, though.
I'm curious to see what kind of moves
helped you get past all those nights?
Don't worry you will!
Come and get it kid this
time I won't go easy on you.
Let's go.
Clever.
Blue Rose Sword.
Lend me your power!
Release Recollection?
Now pay close attention.
The perfect weapon control art has
two stages, enhance and release.
Enhance? Release?
Yes, enhancing awakens part
of your weapon's memories.
The act causes a new attack to manifest.
In the releasing stage, you can
awaken all of your weapon's memories.
Then you can unleash
its most savage power.
Oh, I get it.
That explains Eldrie's win.
In its enhanced stage, it can get
longer than normal, and then split.
Then its release stage was
when it changed into a snake.
You are correct.
That said, you too should avoid
using release for the time being.
Why should we?
Because you are not yet ready to.
You have only just learned of the art.
Until you master it,
you cannot control the power
generated by your weapon's memories.
Especially those of a
divine object like yours.
It can harm you as much as your enemy.
If you're not careful, it will kill you.
I never saw a swordsman toss
his blade during a fight before.
Did you come up with that trick yourself?
Uh-uh.
My partner taught me that one.
The battlefield has lots of opportunities.
Anything can be a weapon or a trap.
Make the best of what you got. Smart.
Well, you might have gotten
the upper hand this round,
but there's no way in
hell you're gonna beat me!
The Blue Rose Sword has two dormant
memories, Eternal Ice and Rose.
When I activate Eternal
Ice, it freezes everything.
Now I'll show you what Rose can do.
Blue Rose Bloom!
What'd you do?
The Rose's bloom by absorbing the
life of those trapped in the ice.
Goddammit, you little punk.
So is this your plan all
along, killing the both of us?
Not us, just you.
You have an advantage over
me in every way except one.
It's your total amount of life left.
Based on your appearance, you became
an Integrity Knight in your 40s.
So, your life value is lower than mine.
I'm younger and my life
value is near its peak.
Even though you landed a hit, the life
I have left is still higher than yours.
That's what I hoped anyway.
Kid, you don't know what
you're talking about.
You just said I became
an Integrity Knight.
A knight's all I've ever been.
I didn't have a life
before I was summoned.
And that's the part of you
people I find so despicable.
You've forgotten who you used to be.
You're loyal to the Axiom Church
without knowing what it really is.
You act like you're champions of
justice, but you uphold corruption.
You think you're here because the
Pontifex summoned you from heaven,
but that's a lie.
You had a mother.
She's the one who gave
you the name Bercouli.
You're human, just like me.
Bercouli.
In my village, they tell stories
about how much of a hero you were.
What stories?
Think back.
I'm sure you've seen this sword before.
Yeah, I have. Somewhere.
Right.
Years ago.
It was in the nest of the white dragon.
I saw it there after I killed it.
You killed the dragon?
I saw its bones.
And now...
Now you say the one who killed it was you.
A dragon that protected the human realm.
The one from your own legend.
Don't you remember
anything about your past?
About who you were?
In Rulid, the village you founded and
where I was born, everyone knew about you.
Young or old, we looked
up to you as a hero.
But the Pontifex sealed
away your memories.
She turned you into the
first Integrity Knight.
Then came the others.
Everyone from Fanatio
to Eldrie, even Alice.
All of you.
Before you became Integrity
Knights, you had lives.
You were human.
Sealed away my memories?
I can't just believe a
wild story like that.
But all that stuff I was told about
me being summoned from heaven And...
I had my doubts...
for a while now.
Well, well.
Now, what do we have here?
This won't do. No, no, no.
This won't do at all, my dear commander.
Surely, good sir, you don't
plan to die on us like this.
That would be treason against her
eminence, the lovely Pontifex.
If she were awake to see you in
this state, she would be livid.
Prime Senator Judalkin, this
is a fight between swordsmen.
A pig like you has no business here.
After going so easy on this heretic,
you have no business
correcting me, dear Commander.
Pray tell, why did you not
use your sword's full power?
If you had,
you could have slaughtered
this loathsome brat
before he opened his
slanderous little mouth.
God, you did not, and therefore committed
treason against the glorious pontifics.
Shut your mouth.
I fought with everything I had.
But you lied to me.
You lied to all of us.
This kid ain't no assassin
from the Dark Territory.
And compared to an ugly piece
of shit like you... Silence!
Be silent or I'll rip off your head!
For your information, my dear,
we wouldn't have this problem?
if you damned knights
weren't so damned useless.
Honestly, when her eminence awakes, you
knights will be thoroughly punished.
At the very least, you and your precious
vice commander shall be reprocessed.
Re-what?
You're talking out your ass again.
System call!
Deep Freeze!
Integrator Unit ID 001!
We don't need old farts like Number
One stinking up the place anymore.
Now we have a much younger, more useful...
Kitty-tops.
Alice.
Eugeo.
Is something the matter?
Huh? Oh, no. Nothing.
As soon as the moon comes out, I think
we can start climbing up the wall again.
Long as I can make spikes, it
should go pretty easy from here on.
There's no minions above us, and
the others here ain't waking up.
For now.
Besides the lack of sacred power,
the only other big problem is food.
I don't know about you, but I'm starving.
If I think about how much further we
gotta go, my head starts spinning.
Could you be any more of
a disappointment? What?
Whether we miss a meal or two
is the least of our worries.
Unless you are a child.
Yeah, well, technically,
I still sort of am.
I might not act like it all the time,
but I'm not even out of my teens yet.
I don't eat, my life goes down.
A problem you badass knights don't have.
Such language.
Even Integrity Knights get hungry.
We must eat or we lose life like you.
Whoa, hold on. Sorry. I was kidding.
Of course you get hungry.
You're as alive as anyone else.
Speaking of food, where
are Cardinal's snacks?
Oh, yeah.
I knew I snagged some more.
Look it.
It's dinner time.
Why in the world would you
store your food in such a way?
I don't.
I just tap my pocket and there they were.
Try it sometime.
But first, I gotta get these ready to eat.
System call.
Generate thermal element.
Burst elements?
Oh, you fool! What?
If you use that art, you will burn them.
Sorry.
Generate thermal element.
Aqueous element.
Aerial element.
Vortex shape.
Burst.
Whoa.
Hurry, give me one.
Wait! No, no, no! I am joking.
That hit the spot.
Thanks for showing me that.
I didn't know you could steam food
using elements instead of a pan.
Did you teach your little sis how to cook?
Cause Selka's really good at it.
What did you say just now?
That you have a little sister?
Her name's Selka.
Sister.
I can tell you about her.
I can tell you everything
I know about this place.
I don't know if you'll believe
me, but it's worth a shot.
Go on, then.
However, if I detect even a trace of deceit
in your words, I shall end your life.
Thank you.
Oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh.
Next time, Recollection.